<?xml version="1.0"?>
<dataset>
<document id="1" name="Reuters-21578-1" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.cocoa</category>
<title>
BAHIA COCOA REVIEW
</title>
<text>
Showers continued throughout the week in
the Bahia cocoa zone, alleviating the drought since early
January and improving prospects for the coming temporao,
although normal humidity levels have not been restored,
Comissaria Smith said in its weekly review.
    The dry period means the temporao will be late this year.
    Arrivals for the week ended February 22 were 155,221 bags
of 60 kilos making a cumulative total for the season of 5.93
mln against 5.81 at the same stage last year. Again it seems
that cocoa delivered earlier on consignment was included in the
arrivals figures.
    Comissaria Smith said there is still some doubt as to how
much old crop cocoa is still available as harvesting has
practically come to an end. With total Bahia crop estimates
around 6.4 mln bags and sales standing at almost 6.2 mln there
are a few hundred thousand bags still in the hands of farmers,
middlemen, exporters and processors.
    There are doubts as to how much of this cocoa would be fit
for export as shippers are now experiencing dificulties in
obtaining +Bahia superior+ certificates.
    In view of the lower quality over recent weeks farmers have
sold a good part of their cocoa held on consignment.
    Comissaria Smith said spot bean prices rose to 340 to 350
cruzados per arroba of 15 kilos.
    Bean shippers were reluctant to offer nearby shipment and
only limited sales were booked for March shipment at 1,750 to
1,780 dlrs per tonne to ports to be named.
    New crop sales were also light and all to open ports with
June/July going at 1,850 and 1,880 dlrs and at 35 and 45 dlrs
under New York july, Aug/Sept at 1,870, 1,875 and 1,880 dlrs
per tonne FOB.
    Routine sales of butter were made. March/April sold at
4,340, 4,345 and 4,350 dlrs.
    April/May butter went at 2.27 times New York May, June/July
at 4,400 and 4,415 dlrs, Aug/Sept at 4,351 to 4,450 dlrs and at
2.27 and 2.28 times New York Sept and Oct/Dec at 4,480 dlrs and
2.27 times New York Dec, Comissaria Smith said.
    Destinations were the U.S., Covertible currency areas,
Uruguay and open ports.
    Cake sales were registered at 785 to 995 dlrs for
March/April, 785 dlrs for May, 753 dlrs for Aug and 0.39 times
New York Dec for Oct/Dec.
    Buyers were the U.S., Argentina, Uruguay and convertible
currency areas.
    Liquor sales were limited with March/April selling at 2,325
and 2,380 dlrs, June/July at 2,375 dlrs and at 1.25 times New
York July, Aug/Sept at 2,400 dlrs and at 1.25 times New York
Sept and Oct/Dec at 1.25 times New York Dec, Comissaria Smith
said.
    Total Bahia sales are currently estimated at 6.13 mln bags
against the 1986/87 crop and 1.06 mln bags against the 1987/88
crop.
    Final figures for the period to February 28 are expected to
be published by the Brazilian Cocoa Trade Commission after
carnival which ends midday on February 27.
</text>
</document>
<document id="5" name="Reuters-21578-5" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.sorghum</category>
<category>topics.oat</category>
<category>topics.barley</category>
<category>topics.corn</category>
<category>topics.wheat</category>
<category>topics.grain</category>
<title>
NATIONAL AVERAGE PRICES FOR FARMER-OWNED RESERVE
</title>
<text>
The U.S. Agriculture Department
reported the farmer-owned reserve national five-day average
price through February 25 as follows (Dlrs/Bu-Sorghum Cwt) -
         Natl   Loan           Release   Call
         Avge   Rate-X  Level    Price  Price
 Wheat   2.55   2.40       IV     4.65     --
                            V     4.65     --
                           VI     4.45     --
 Corn    1.35   1.92       IV     3.15   3.15
                            V     3.25     --
 X - 1986 Rates.
          Natl   Loan          Release   Call
          Avge   Rate-X  Level   Price  Price
 Oats     1.24   0.99        V    1.65    -- 
 Barley   n.a.   1.56       IV    2.55   2.55
                             V    2.65    -- 
 Sorghum  2.34   3.25-Y     IV    5.36   5.36
                             V    5.54    -- 
    Reserves I, II and III have matured. Level IV reflects
grain entered after Oct 6, 1981 for feedgrain and after July
23, 1981 for wheat. Level V wheat/barley after 5/14/82,
corn/sorghum after 7/1/82. Level VI covers wheat entered after
January 19, 1984.  X-1986 rates. Y-dlrs per CWT (100 lbs).
n.a.-not available.
</text>
</document>
<document id="6" name="Reuters-21578-6" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.wheat</category>
<category>topics.sorghum</category>
<category>topics.grain</category>
<category>topics.sunseed</category>
<category>topics.corn</category>
<category>topics.oilseed</category>
<category>topics.soybean</category>
<category>topics.sun-oil</category>
<category>topics.soy-oil</category>
<category>topics.lin-oil</category>
<category>topics.veg-oil</category>
<title>
ARGENTINE 1986/87 GRAIN/OILSEED REGISTRATIONS
</title>
<text>
Argentine grain board figures show
crop registrations of grains, oilseeds and their products to
February 11, in thousands of tonnes, showing those for futurE
shipments month, 1986/87 total and 1985/86 total to February
12, 1986, in brackets:
    Bread wheat prev 1,655.8, Feb 872.0, March 164.6, total
2,692.4 (4,161.0).
    Maize Mar 48.0, total 48.0 (nil).
    Sorghum nil (nil)
    Oilseed export registrations were:
    Sunflowerseed total 15.0 (7.9)
    Soybean May 20.0, total 20.0 (nil)
    The board also detailed export registrations for
subproducts, as follows,
    SUBPRODUCTS
    Wheat prev 39.9, Feb 48.7, March 13.2, Apr 10.0, total
111.8 (82.7) .
    Linseed prev 34.8, Feb 32.9, Mar 6.8, Apr 6.3, total 80.8
(87.4).
    Soybean prev 100.9, Feb 45.1, MAr nil, Apr nil, May 20.0,
total 166.1 (218.5).
    Sunflowerseed prev 48.6, Feb 61.5, Mar 25.1, Apr 14.5,
total 149.8 (145.3).
    Vegetable oil registrations were :         
    Sunoil prev 37.4, Feb 107.3, Mar 24.5, Apr 3.2, May nil,
Jun 10.0, total 182.4 (117.6).                  
    Linoil prev 15.9, Feb 23.6, Mar 20.4, Apr 2.0, total 61.8,
(76.1).                         
    Soybean oil prev 3.7, Feb 21.1, Mar nil, Apr 2.0, May 9.0,
Jun 13.0, Jul 7.0, total 55.8 (33.7).        REUTER
</text>
</document>
<document id="9" name="Reuters-21578-9" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
CHAMPION PRODUCTS &lt;CH> APPROVES STOCK SPLIT
</title>
<text>
Champion Products Inc said its
board of directors approved a two-for-one stock split of its
common shares for shareholders of record as of April 1, 1987.
    The company also said its board voted to recommend to
shareholders at the annual meeting April 23 an increase in the
authorized capital stock from five mln to 25 mln shares.
</text>
</document>
<document id="10" name="Reuters-21578-10" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.acq</category>
<title>
COMPUTER TERMINAL SYSTEMS &lt;CPML> COMPLETES SALE
</title>
<text>
Computer Terminal Systems Inc said
it has completed the sale of 200,000 shares of its common
stock, and warrants to acquire an additional one mln shares, to
&lt;Sedio N.V.> of Lugano, Switzerland for 50,000 dlrs.
    The company said the warrants are exercisable for five
years at a purchase price of .125 dlrs per share.
    Computer Terminal said Sedio also has the right to buy
additional shares and increase its total holdings up to 40 pct
of the Computer Terminal's outstanding common stock under
certain circumstances involving change of control at the
company.
    The company said if the conditions occur the warrants would
be exercisable at a price equal to 75 pct of its common stock's
market price at the time, not to exceed 1.50 dlrs per share.
    Computer Terminal also said it sold the technolgy rights to
its Dot Matrix impact technology, including any future
improvements, to &lt;Woodco Inc> of Houston, Tex. for 200,000
dlrs. But, it said it would continue to be the exclusive
worldwide licensee of the technology for Woodco.
    The company said the moves were part of its reorganization
plan and would help pay current operation costs and ensure
product delivery.
    Computer Terminal makes computer generated labels, forms,
tags and ticket printers and terminals.
</text>
</document>
<document id="11" name="Reuters-21578-11" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
COBANCO INC &lt;CBCO> YEAR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 34 cts vs 1.19 dlrs
    Net 807,000 vs 2,858,000
    Assets 510.2 mln vs 479.7 mln
    Deposits 472.3 mln vs 440.3 mln
    Loans 299.2 mln vs 327.2 mln
    Note: 4th qtr not available. Year includes 1985
extraordinary gain from tax carry forward of 132,000 dlrs, or
five cts per shr.
</text>
</document>
<document id="12" name="Reuters-21578-12" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.acq</category>
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
OHIO MATTRESS &lt;OMT> MAY HAVE LOWER 1ST QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Ohio Mattress Co said its first
quarter, ending February 28, profits may be below the 2.4 mln
dlrs, or 15 cts a share, earned in the first quarter of fiscal
1986.
    The company said any decline would be due to expenses
related to the acquisitions in the middle of the current
quarter of seven licensees of Sealy Inc, as well as 82 pct of
the outstanding capital stock of Sealy.
    Because of these acquisitions, it said, first quarter sales
will be substantially higher than last year's 67.1 mln dlrs.
    Noting that it typically reports first quarter results in
late march, said the report is likely to be issued in early
April this year.
    It said the delay is due to administrative considerations,
including conducting appraisals, in connection with the
acquisitions.
</text>
</document>
<document id="13" name="Reuters-21578-13" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
AM INTERNATIONAL INC &lt;AM> 2ND QTR JAN 31
</title>
<text>
Oper shr loss two cts vs profit seven cts
    Oper shr profit 442,000 vs profit 2,986,000
    Revs 291.8 mln vs 151.1 mln
    Avg shrs 51.7 mln vs 43.4 mln
    Six mths
    Oper shr profit nil vs profit 12 cts
    Oper net profit 3,376,000 vs profit 5,086,000
    Revs 569.3 mln vs 298.5 mln
    Avg shrs 51.6 mln vs 41.1 mln
    NOTE: Per shr calculated after payment of preferred
dividends.
    Results exclude credits of 2,227,000 or four cts and
4,841,000 or nine cts for 1986 qtr and six mths vs 2,285,000 or
six cts and 4,104,000 or 11 cts for prior periods from
operating loss carryforwards.
</text>
</document>
<document id="14" name="Reuters-21578-14" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
BROWN-FORMAN INC &lt;BFD> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr one dlr vs 73 cts
    Net 12.6 mln vs 15.8 mln
    Revs 337.3 mln vs 315.2 mln
    Nine mths
    Shr 3.07 dlrs vs 3.08 dlrs
    Net 66 mln vs 66.2 mln
    Revs 1.59 billion vs 997.1 mln
</text>
</document>
<document id="18" name="Reuters-21578-18" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
DEAN FOODS &lt;DF> SEES STRONG 4TH QTR EARNINGS
</title>
<text>
Dean Foods Co expects earnings for the
fourth quarter ending May 30 to exceed those of the same
year-ago period, Chairman Kenneth Douglas told analysts.
    In the fiscal 1986 fourth quarter the food processor
reported earnings of 40 cts a share.
    Douglas also said the year's sales should exceed 1.4
billion dlrs, up from 1.27 billion dlrs the prior year.
    He repeated an earlier projection that third-quarter
earnings "will probably be off slightly" from last year's 40
cts a share, falling in the range of 34 cts to 36 cts a share.
    Douglas said it was too early to project whether the
anticipated fourth quarter performance would be "enough for us
to exceed the prior year's overall earnings" of 1.53 dlrs a
share.
    In 1988, Douglas said Dean should experience "a 20 pct
improvement in our bottom line from effects of the tax reform
act alone."
    President Howard Dean said in fiscal 1988 the company will
derive  benefits of various dairy and frozen vegetable
acquisitions from Ryan Milk to the Larsen Co.
    Dean also said the company will benefit from its
acquisition in late December of Elgin Blenders Inc, West
Chicago.
    He said the company is a major shareholder of E.B.I. Foods
Ltd, a United Kingdom blender, and has licensing arrangements
in Australia, Canada, Brazil and Japan.
    "It provides ann entry to McDonalds Corp &lt;MCD> we've been
after for years," Douglas told analysts.
</text>
</document>
<document id="19" name="Reuters-21578-19" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.grain</category>
<category>topics.wheat</category>
<title>
BONUS WHEAT FLOUR FOR NORTH YEMEN  -- USDA
</title>
<text>
The Commodity Credit Corporation, CCC,
has accepted an export bonus offer to cover the sale of 37,000
long tons of wheat flour to North Yemen, the U.S. Agriculture
Department said.
    The wheat four is for shipment March-May and the bonus
awarded was 119.05 dlrs per tonnes and will be paid in the form
of commodities from the CCC inventory.
    The bonus was awarded to the Pillsbury Company.
    The wheat flour purchases complete the Export Enhancement
Program initiative announced in April, 1986, it said.
</text>
</document>
<document id="22" name="Reuters-21578-22" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.copper</category>
<title>
MAGMA LOWERS COPPER 0.75 CENT TO 66 CTS
</title>
<text>
Magma Copper Co, a subsidiary of Newmont
Mining Corp, said it is cutting its copper cathode price by
0.75 cent to 66 cents a lb, effective immediately.
</text>
</document>
<document id="23" name="Reuters-21578-23" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
BROWN-FORMAN &lt;BFDB> SETS STOCK SPLIT, UPS PAYOUT
</title>
<text>
Brown-Forman Inc said its board
has approved a three-for-two stock split and a 35 pct increase
in the company cash dividend.
    The company cited its improved earnings outlook and
continued strong cash flow as reasons for raising the dividend.
    Brown-Forman said the split of its Class A and Class B
common shares would be effective March 13.
    The company said directors declared a quarterly cash
dividend on each new share of both classes of 28 cts, payable
April one to holders of record March 20. Prior to the split,
the company had paid 31 cts quarterly.
    Brown-Forman today reported a 37 pct increase in third 
quarter profits to 21.6 mln dlrs, or 1.00 dlr a share, on a
seven pct increase in sales to a record 337 mln dlrs.
    Brown-Forman said nine month profits declined a bit to 66.0
mln dlrs, or 3.07 dlrs a share, from 66.2 mln dlrs, or 3.08
dlrs a share, a year earlier due to a second quarter charge of
37 cts a share for restructuring its beverage operations.
    The company said lower corporate tax rates and the
restructuring "are expected to substantially improve
Brown-Forman's earnings and cash flow in fiscal 1988."
</text>
</document>
<document id="24" name="Reuters-21578-24" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
ESQUIRE RADIO AND ELECTRONICS INC &lt;EE> 4TH QTR
</title>
<text>
Shr profit 15 cts vs profit four cts
    Annual div 72 cts vs 72 cts prior yr
    Net profit 72,000 vs profit 16,000
    Revs 7,075,000 vs 2,330,000
    12 mths
    Shr profit 42 cts vs loss 11 cts
    Net profit 203,000 vs loss 55,000
    Revs 16.1 mln vs 3,971,000
    NOTE: annual dividend payable April 10, 1987, to
stockholders of record on March 27, 1987.
</text>
</document>
<document id="27" name="Reuters-21578-27" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
UNITED PRESIDENTIAL CORP &lt;UPCO> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 39 cts vs 50 cts
    Net 1,545,160 vs 2,188,933
    Revs 25.2 mln vs 19.5 mln
    Year
    Shr 1.53 dlrs vs 1.21 dlrs
    Net 6,635,318 vs 5,050,044
    Revs 92.2 mln vs 77.4 mln
    NOTE: Results include adjustment of 848,600 dlrs or 20 cts
shr for 1986 year and both 1985 periods from improvement in
results of its universal life business than first estimated.
</text>
</document>
<document id="29" name="Reuters-21578-29" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.housing</category>
<title>
JANUARY HOUSING SALES DROP, REALTY GROUP SAYS
</title>
<text>
Sales of previously owned homes
dropped 14.5 pct in January to a seasonally adjusted annual
rate of 3.47 mln units, the National Association of Realtors
(NAR) said.
    But the December rate of 4.06 mln units had been the
highest since the record 4.15 mln unit sales rate set in
November 1978, the group said.
    "The drop in January is not surprising considering that a
significant portion of December's near-record pace was made up
of sellers seeking to get favorable capital gains treatment
under the old tax laws," said the NAR's John Tuccillo.
</text>
</document>
<document id="30" name="Reuters-21578-30" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
ASSETS OF MONEY MARKET MUTUAL FUNDS ROSE 720.4 MLN DLRS IN LATEST WEEK
</title>
<text>
ASSETS OF MONEY MARKET MUTUAL FUNDS ROSE 720.4 MLN DLRS IN LATEST WEEK
</text>
</document>
<document id="36" name="Reuters-21578-36" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
OWENS AND MINOR INC &lt;OBOD> RAISES QTLY DIVIDEND
</title>
<text>
Qtly div eights cts vs 7.5 cts prior
    Pay March 31
    Record March 13
</text>
</document>
<document id="37" name="Reuters-21578-37" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
COMPUTER LANGUAGE RESEARCH IN &lt;CLRI> 4TH QTR
</title>
<text>
Shr loss 22 cts vs loss 18 cts
    Net loss 3,035,000 vs loss 2,516,000
    Revs 20.9 mln vs 19.6 mln
    Qtly div three cts vs three cts prior
    Year
    Shr profit two cts vs profit 34 cts
    Net profit 215,000 vs profit 4,647,000
    Revs 93.4 mln vs 98.7 mln
    NOTE: Dividend payable April one to shareholders of record
March 17.
</text>
</document>
<document id="38" name="Reuters-21578-38" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
&lt;CINRAM LTD> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 45 cts vs 58 cts
    Net 1.1 mln vs 829,000
    Sales 7.9 mln vs 9.4 mln
    Avg shrs 2,332,397 vs 1,428,000
    Year
    Shr 1.22 dlrs vs 1.06 dlrs
    Net 2.9 mln vs 1.5 mln
    Sales 25.7 mln vs 22.2 mln
    Avg shrs 2,332,397 vs 1,428,000
</text>
</document>
<document id="40" name="Reuters-21578-40" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
STANDARD TRUSTCO SEES BETTER YEAR
</title>
<text>
Standard Trustco said it expects earnings
in 1987 to increase at least 15 to 20 pct from the 9,140,000
dlrs, or 2.52 dlrs per share, recorded in 1986.
    "Stable interest rates and a growing economy are expected to
provide favorable conditions for further growth in 1987,"
president Brian O'Malley told shareholders at the annual
meeting.
    Standard Trustco previously reported assets of 1.28 billion
dlrs in 1986, up from 1.10 billion dlrs in 1985. Return on
common shareholders' equity was 18.6 pct last year, up from 15
pct in 1985.
</text>
</document>
<document id="41" name="Reuters-21578-41" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
HANDY AND HARMAN &lt;HNH> 4TH QTR LOSS
</title>
<text>
Shr loss 51 cts vs loss three cts
    Net loss 7,041,000 vs loss 467,000
    Rev 138.9 mln vs 131.4 mln
    12 months
    Shr loss 64 cts vs profit 46 cts
    Net loss 8,843,000 vs profit 6,306,0000
    Rev 558.9 mln vs 556.7 mln
    NOTE: Net loss for 4th qtr 1986 includes charge for
restructuring of 2.6 mln dlrs after tax, or 19 cts a share.
    1986 net loss includes after tax special charge of 2.7 mln
dlrs, or 20 cts a share.
</text>
</document>
<document id="42" name="Reuters-21578-42" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.coffee</category>
<title>
ICO PRODUCERS TO PRESENT NEW COFFEE PROPOSAL
</title>
<text>
International Coffee Organization, ICO,
producing countries will present a proposal for reintroducing
export quotas for 12 months from April 1 with a firm
undertaking to try to negotiate up to September 30 any future
quota distribution on a new basis, ICO delegates said.
    Distribution from April 1 would be on an unchanged basis as
in an earlier producer proposal, which includes shortfall
redistributions totalling 1.22 mln bags, they said.
    Resumption of an ICO contact group meeting with consumers,
scheduled for this evening, has been postponed until tomorrow,
delegates said.
</text>
</document>
<document id="44" name="Reuters-21578-44" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.ship</category>
<category>topics.acq</category>
<title>
MCLEAN'S &lt;MII> U.S. LINES SETS ASSET TRANSFER
</title>
<text>
McLean Industries Inc's United
States Lines Inc subsidiary said it has agreed in principle to
transfer its South American service by arranging for the
transfer of certain charters and assets to &lt;Crowley Mariotime
Corp>'s American Transport Lines Inc subsidiary.
    U.S. Lines said negotiations on the contract are expected
to be completed within the next week. Terms and conditions of
the contract would be subject to approval of various regulatory
bodies, including the U.S. Bankruptcy Court.
</text>
</document>
<document id="45" name="Reuters-21578-45" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.acq</category>
<title>
CHEMLAWN &lt;CHEM> RISES ON HOPES FOR HIGHER BIDS
</title>
<text>
ChemLawn Corp &lt;CHEM> could attract a
higher bid than the 27 dlrs per share offered by Waste
Management Inc &lt;WNX>, Wall Street arbitrageurs said.
    Shares of ChemLawn shot up 11-5/8 to 29-3/8 in
over-the-counter- trading with 3.8 mln of the company's 10.1
mln shares changing hands by late afternoon.
    "This company could go for 10 times cash flow or 30 dlrs,
maybe 32 dollars depending on whether there is a competing
bidder," an arbitrageur said. Waste Management's tender offer,
announced before the opening today, expires March 25.
    "This is totally by surprise," said Debra Strohmaier, a
ChemLawn spokeswoman. The company's board held a regularly
scheduled meeting today and was discussing the Waste Management
announcement. She said a statement was expected but it was not
certain when it would be ready. 
    She was unable to say if there had been any prior contact
between Waste Management and ChemLawn officials.
    "I think they will resist it," said Elliott Schlang,
analyst at Prescott, Ball and Turben Inc. "Any company that
doesn't like a surprise attack would."
    Arbitrageurs pointed out it is difficult to resist tender
offers for any and all shares for cash. Schlang said ChemLawn
could try to find a white knight if does not want to be
acquired by Waste Management.
    Analyst Rosemarie Morbelli of Ingalls and Snyder said
ServiceMaster Companies L.P. &lt;SVM> or Rollins Inc &lt;ROL> were
examples of companies that could be interested.
    ChemLawn, with about two mln customers, is the largest U.S.
company involved in application of fertilizers, pesticides and
herbicides on lawns. Waste Management is involved in removal of
wastes.
    Schlang said ChemLawn's customer base could be valuable to
another company that wants to capitalize on a strong
residential and commercial distribution system.
    Both Schlang and Morbelli noted that high growth rates had
catapulted ChemLawn's share price into the mid-30's in 1983 but
the stock languished as the rate of growth slowed.
    Schlang said the company's profits are concentrated in the
fourth quarter. In 1986 ChemLawn earned 1.19 dlrs per share for
the full year, and 2.58 dlrs in the fourth quarter.
    Morbelli noted ChemLawn competes with thousands of
individual entrepreuers who offer lawn and garden care sevice.
</text>
</document>
<document id="46" name="Reuters-21578-46" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.sugar</category>
<title>
U.S. SUGAR IMPORTS DOWN IN WEEK - USDA
</title>
<text>
Sugar imports subject to the U.S.
sugar import quota during the week ended January 9, the initial
week of the 1987 sugar quota year, totaled 5,988 short tons
versus 46,254 tons the previous week, the Agriculture
Department said.
    The sugar import quota for the 1987 quota year
(January-December) has been set at 1,001,430 short tons
compared with 1,850,000 tons in the 1986 quota year, which was
extended three months to December 31.
    The department said the Customs Service has reported that
weekly and cumulative imports are reported on an actual weight
basis and when final polarizations are received, cumulative
import data are adjusted accordingly.
</text>
</document>
<document id="47" name="Reuters-21578-47" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.trade</category>
<title>
BRAZIL ANTI-INFLATION PLAN LIMPS TO ANNIVERSARY
</title>
<text>
inflation
plan, initially hailed at home and abroad as the saviour of the
economy, is limping towards its first anniversary amid soaring
prices, widespread shortages and a foreign payments crisis.
    Announced last February 28 the plan froze prices, fixed the
value of the new Cruzado currency and ended widespread
indexation of the economy in a bid to halt the country's 250
pct inflation rate.
    But within a year the plan has all but collapsed.
    "The situation now is worse than it was. Although there was
inflation, at least the economy worked," a leading bank
economist said.
    The crumbling of the plan has been accompanied by a
dramatic reversal in the foreign trade account. In 1984 and
1985 Brazil's annual trade surpluses had been sufficient to
cover the 12 billion dlrs needed to service its 109 billion dlr
foreign debt.
    For the first nine months of 1986 all seemed to be on
target for a repeat, with monthly surpluses averaging one
billion dlrs. But as exports were diverted and imports
increased to avoid further domestic shortages the trade surplus
plunged to 211 mln dlrs in October and since then has averaged
under 150 mln.
</text>
</document>
<document id="48" name="Reuters-21578-48" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.reserves</category>
<title>
N.Z. OFFICIAL FOREIGN RESERVES FALL IN JANUARY
</title>
<text>
New Zealand's official foreign
reserves fell to 7.15 billion N.Z. Dlrs in January from 7.20
billion dlrs in December and compared with 3.03 billion a year
ago period, the Reserve Bank said in its weekly statistical
bulletin.
</text>
</document>
<document id="49" name="Reuters-21578-49" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.ship</category>
<title>
AGENCY REPORTS 39 SHIPS WAITING AT PANAMA CANAL
</title>
<text>
The Panama Canal Commission, a U.S.
government agency, said in its daily operations report that
there was a backlog of 39 ships waiting to enter the canal
early today. Over the next two days it expects --              
             2/26  2/27
                       Due: 27    35
      Scheduled to Transit: 35    41
           End-Day Backlog: 31    25
    Average waiting time tomorrow --
         Super Tankers  Regular Vessels
 North End:  13 hrs      15 hrs
 South End:   4 hrs      26 hrs
</text>
</document>
<document id="50" name="Reuters-21578-50" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
AMERICA FIRST MORTGAGE SETS SPECIAL PAYOUT
</title>
<text>
&lt;America First Federally Guaranteed
Mortgage Fund Two> said it is making a special distribution of
71.6 cts per exchangeable unit, which includes 67.62 cts from
return on capital and 3.98 cts from income gains.
</text>
</document>
<document id="53" name="Reuters-21578-53" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
EMHART CORP &lt;EMH> QTLY DIVIDEND
</title>
<text>
Qtly div 35 cts vs 35 cts prior
    Payable March 31
    Record March nine
</text>
</document>
<document id="56" name="Reuters-21578-56" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
AM INTERNATIONAL &lt;AM> CITES STRONG PROSPECTS
</title>
<text>
AM International Inc, reporting an
operating loss for the January 31 second quarter, said
prospects for the balance of the fiscal year remain good.
    It said orders at its Harris Graphics subsidiary, acquired
in June 1986, "continue to run at a strong pace." For the six
months, orders rose 35 pct over the corresponding prior-year
period, or on an annualized basis are running at about 630 mln
dlrs.
    The backlog at Harris is up 30 pct from the beginning of
the fiscal year, AM said.
    AM International said its old division are expected to
benefit from recent new product introductions and the decline
in the value of the dollar.
    "Research, development and engineering expenditures in
fiscal 1987 will be in the 45-50 mln dlr range, and the company
said it has allocated another 30-40 mln dlrs for capital
expenditures.
    Earlier AM reported a fourth quarter operating loss of two
cts a share compared to profits of seven cts a share a year
ago. Revenues rose to 291.8 mln dlrs from 151.1 mln dlrs.
</text>
</document>
<document id="57" name="Reuters-21578-57" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.corn</category>
<category>topics.grain</category>
<title>
CCC CREDITS FOR HONDURAS SWITCHED TO WHITE CORN
</title>
<text>
The Commodity Credit Corporation (CCC)
announced 1.5 mln dlrs in credit guarantees previously
earmarked to cover sales of dry edible beans to Honduras have
been switched to cover sales of white corn, the U.S.
Agriculture Department said.
    The department said the action reduces coverage for sales
of dry edible beans to 500,000 dlrs and creates the new line of
1.5 mln dlrs for sales of white corn.
    All sales under the credit guarantee line must be
registered  and shipped by September 30, 1987, it said.
</text>
</document>
<document id="58" name="Reuters-21578-58" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
ASSETS OF U.S. MONEY FUNDS ROSE IN WEEK
</title>
<text>
Assets of money market mutual funds
increased 720.4 mln dlrs in the week ended yesterday to 236.90
billion dlrs, the Investment Company Institute said.
    Assets of 91 institutional funds rose 356 mln dlrs to 66.19
billion dlrs, 198 general purpose funds rose 212.5 mln dlrs to
62.94 billion dlrs and 92 broker-dealer funds rose 151.9 mln
dlrs to 107.77 billion dlrs.
</text>
</document>
<document id="59" name="Reuters-21578-59" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.ship</category>
<title>
GULF BARGE FREIGHT RATES UP FURTHER ON CALL
</title>
<text>
Gulf barge freight rates firmed again on
the outlook for steady vessel loadings at the Gulf, increasing
the demand for barges to supply those ships, dealers said.
    No barges traded today on the St Louis Merchants' Exchange
call session, versus 29 yesterday.
    Quotes included -
 - Delivery this week on the Illinois River (Joliet) 135 pct of
tariff bid/140 offered, with next week same river (ex Chicago)
quoted the same - both up 2-1/2 percentage points.
 - Next week Mississippi River (St Louis) 120 pct bid/127-1/2
offered - up five points.
 - Next week Ohio River (Owensboro/south) 125 pct bid/132-1/2
offered - up 7-1/2 points.
 - On station Illinois River (south Chicago) 135 pct bid/140
offered - no comparison.
 - March Illinois (ex Chicago) 132-1/2 pct bid/140 offered - up
2-1/2 points.
 - March Ohio River bid at yesterday's traded level of 125 pct,
offered at 132-1/2.
 - March lower Mississippi River (Memphis/Cairo) 112-1/2 pct
bid/120 offered - no comparison.
 - May Illinois River (ex Chicago) 100 pct bid/107-1/2 offered
- no comparison.
 - Sept/Nov Lower Mississippi River (Memphis/Cairo) 137-1/2 pct
bid/145 offered, with Sept/Dec same section 125 pct bid/135
offered - no comparison.
</text>
</document>
<document id="64" name="Reuters-21578-64" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
GULF APPLIED &lt;GATS> SELLS UNITS, SEES GAIN
</title>
<text>
Gulf Applied Technologies Inc said it
sold its pipeline and terminal operations units for 12.2 mln
dlrs and will record a gain of 2.9 mln dlrs in the first
quarter.
    It added that any federal taxes owed on the transaction
will be offset by operating loss carryovers.
</text>
</document>
<document id="65" name="Reuters-21578-65" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
FARMERS GROUP INC &lt;FGRP> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 80 cts vs 72 cts
    Net 55,513,000 vs 48,741,000
    Revs 290.9 mln vs 264.2 mln
    Year
    Shr 3.09 dlrs vs 2.72 dlrs
    Net 213,470,000 vs 184,649,000
    Revs 1.12 billion vs 992.9 mln
    Avg shrs 69,127,000 vs 68,004,000
</text>
</document>
<document id="66" name="Reuters-21578-66" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
POTOMAC ELECTRIC POWER CO &lt;POM> JAN NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 27 cts vs 29 cts
    Net 13,555,000 vs 14,635,000
    Revs 104,606,000 vs 110,311,000
    Avg shrs 47.2 mln vs 47.1 mln
    12 mths
    Shr 4.10 dlrs vs 3.66 dlrs
    Net 226,653,000 vs 186,790,000
    Revs 1.4 billion vs 1.3 billion
    Avg shr 47.1 mln vs 47.1 mln
    NOTE: latest 12 mths net includes gain 46 cts per share for
sale of Virginia service territory to Dominion Resources Inc
&lt;D>.
</text>
</document>
<document id="68" name="Reuters-21578-68" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.acq</category>
<title>
&lt;COFAB INC> BUYS GULFEX FOR UNDISCLOSED AMOUNT
</title>
<text>
CoFAB Inc said it acquired &lt;Gulfex Inc>,
a Houston-based fabricator of custom high-pressure process
vessels for the energy and petrochemical industries.
    CoFAB said its group of companies manufacture specialized
cooling and lubricating systems for the oil and gas,
petrochemical, utility, pulp and paper and marine industries.
</text>
</document>
<document id="69" name="Reuters-21578-69" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.soy-meal</category>
<category>topics.meal-feed</category>
<category>topics.oilseed</category>
<category>topics.soybean</category>
<category>topics.veg-oil</category>
<title>
U.S. WEEKLY SOYBEAN CRUSH 21,782,929 BUSHELS
</title>
<text>
Reporting members of the National
Soybean Processors Association (NSPA) crushed 21,782,929
bushels of soybeans in the week ended Feb 25 compared with
22,345,718 bushels in the previous week and 16,568,000 in the
year-ago week, the association said.
    It said total crushing capacity for members was 25,873,904
bushels vs 25,873,904 last week and 25,459,238 bushels last
year.
    NSPA also said U.S. soybean meal exports in the week were
117,866 tonnes vs 121,168 tonnes a week ago and compared with
84,250 tonnes in the year-ago week.
    NSPA said the figures include only NSPA member firms.
</text>
</document>
<document id="71" name="Reuters-21578-71" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
TULTEX CORP &lt;TTX> SETS QUARTERLY DIVIDEND
</title>
<text>
Qtly div eights cts vs eight cts prior
    Pay April one
    Record March 13
</text>
</document>
<document id="74" name="Reuters-21578-74" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
ATICO FINANCIAL CORP &lt;ATFC> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 30 cts vs 5.92 dlrs
    Net 1,142,000 vs 16.0 mln
    Revs 10.6 mln vs 24.2 mln
    Year
    Shr 90 cts vs 6.20 dlrs
    Net 3,320,000 vs 16.9 mln
    Revs 45.00 mln vs 26.2 mln
    NOTE: 1986 4th qtr and yr amounts include acquisition of
98.8 pct of common of Atico, formerly Peninsula Federal Savings
and Loan Association, on January 24, 1986.
    1985 4th qtr and yr net include net gain of 15.9 mln dlrs
or 5.86 dlrs per share on exchange of common of Pan America
Banks Inc for common of NCNB Corp purusant to a merger of the
companies.
</text>
</document>
<document id="75" name="Reuters-21578-75" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.coffee</category>
<title>
ICO EXPORTERS TO MODIFY NEW PROPOSAL
</title>
<text>
International Coffee Organization (ICO)
exporters will modify their new proposal on quota resumption
before presenting it to importers tomorrow, ICO delegates said.
    The change, which will be discussed tonight informally
among producers, follows talks after the formal producer
session with the eight-member producer splinter group and will
affect the proposed quota distribution for 12 months from April
one, they said.
    The proposed share-out would still include shortfall
declarations, they said.
</text>
</document>
<document id="76" name="Reuters-21578-76" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
U.S. COMMERCIAL PAPER FALLS 375 MLN DLRS IN FEB 18 WEEK, FED SAYS
</title>
<text>
U.S. COMMERCIAL PAPER FALLS 375 MLN DLRS IN FEB 18 WEEK, FED SAYS
</text>
</document>
<document id="77" name="Reuters-21578-77" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
N.Y. BUSINESS LOANS FALL 195 MLN DLRS IN FEB 18 WEEK, FED SAYS
</title>
<text>
N.Y. BUSINESS LOANS FALL 195 MLN DLRS IN FEB 18 WEEK, FED SAYS
</text>
</document>
<document id="78" name="Reuters-21578-78" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
NEW YORK BANK DISCOUNT WINDOW BORROWINGS 64 MLN DLRS IN FEB 25 WEEK
</title>
<text>
NEW YORK BANK DISCOUNT WINDOW BORROWINGS 64 MLN DLRS IN FEB 25 WEEK
</text>
</document>
<document id="80" name="Reuters-21578-80" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
NEW YORK BUSINESS LOANS FALL 195 MLN DLRS
</title>
<text>
Commercial and industrial loans on the
books of the 10 major New York banks, excluding acceptances,
fell 195 mln dlrs to 65.06 billion in the week ended February
18, the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said.
    Including acceptances, loans declined 114 mln dlrs to 65.89
billion.
    Commercial paper outstanding nationally dropped 375 mln
dlrs to 336.63 billion.
    National business loan data are scheduled to be released on
Friday.
</text>
</document>
<document id="81" name="Reuters-21578-81" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
N.Y. BANK DISCOUNT BORROWINGS 64 MLN DLRS
</title>
<text>
The eight major New York City banks had
64 mln dlrs in average borrowings from the Federal Reserve in
the week to Wednesday February 25, a Fed spokesman said.
    The week marked the second half of the two-week bank
statement period that ended on Wednesday. The banks had no
borrowings in the prior week.
    Commenting on the latest week, a Fed spokesman said that
all of the borrowing occurred yesterday and was done by fewer
than half of the banks.
    National data on discount window borrowings are due to be
released at 1630 EST (2130 GMT).
</text>
</document>
<document id="82" name="Reuters-21578-82" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
PHILIPPINE LONG DISTANCE &lt;PHI> YEAR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr primary 95.30 pesos vs 29.71 pesos
    Shr diluted 61.11 pesos vs 18.49 pesos
    Qtly div 1.25 pesos vs 1.25 pesos
    Net 1.9 billion vs 779 mln
    Revs 6.1 billion vs 4.7 billion
    NOTE: Full name Philippine Long Distance Telephone Co.
    Figures quoted in Philippine Pesos.
    Dividend payable April 15 to holders or record March 13.
Exchange rate on day of dividend declaration was 20.792 pesos
per dollar.
</text>
</document>
<document id="83" name="Reuters-21578-83" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
LIBERTY ALL-STAR EQUITY FUND INITIAL DIV
</title>
<text>
Qtly div five cts vs N.A.
    Payable April two
    Record March 20
    NOTE:1986 dividend includes special two cts per share for
the period beginning with the fund's commencement of operations
on Novebmer three through December 31, 1986.
</text>
</document>
<document id="85" name="Reuters-21578-85" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
COMBUSTION ENGINEERING INC &lt;CSP> REGULAR DIV
</title>
<text>
Qtly div 25 cts vs 25 cts prior
    Pay April 30
    Record April 16
</text>
</document>
<document id="86" name="Reuters-21578-86" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
TONKA CORP &lt;TKA> RAISES DIVIDEND
</title>
<text>
Qtly div two cts vs 1.7 cts
    Pay March 26
    Record March 12
</text>
</document>
<document id="87" name="Reuters-21578-87" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
BDM INTERNATIONAL &lt;BDM> INCREASES QTRLY DIVS
</title>
<text>
Annual div Class A 14 cts vs 12 cts prior
    Annual div Class B 12.1 cts vs 10.4 cts prior
    Payable April one
    Record March 20
    NOTE: full name is BDM International Inc.
</text>
</document>
<document id="89" name="Reuters-21578-89" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
SYSTEMATICS INC &lt;SYST> REGULAR PAYOUT
</title>
<text>
Qtly div three cts vs three cts prior
    Pay March 13
    Record February 27
</text>
</document>
<document id="92" name="Reuters-21578-92" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
U.S. M-1 MONEY SUPPLY RISES 2.1 BILLION DLRS IN FEB 16 WEEK, FED SAYS
</title>
<text>
U.S. M-1 MONEY SUPPLY RISES 2.1 BILLION DLRS IN FEB 16 WEEK, FED SAYS
</text>
</document>
<document id="93" name="Reuters-21578-93" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
&lt;IVACO INC> YEAR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr 1.11 dlrs vs 1.04 dlrs
    Net 44,092,000 vs 35,145,000
    Revs 1.94 billion vs 1.34 billion
    Note: 1986 results include extraordinary gain of 1,035,000
dlrs or six cts a share from secondary share offering of Canron
unit.
</text>
</document>
<document id="94" name="Reuters-21578-94" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
U.S. BANK DISCOUNT BORROWINGS AVERAGE 310 MLN DLRS IN FEB 25 WEEK, FED SAYS
</title>
<text>
U.S. BANK DISCOUNT BORROWINGS AVERAGE 310 MLN DLRS IN FEB 25 WEEK, FED SAYS
</text>
</document>
<document id="95" name="Reuters-21578-95" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
U.S. BANK NET FREE RESERVES 644 MLN DLRS IN TWO WEEKS TO FEB 25, FED SAYS
</title>
<text>
U.S. BANK NET FREE RESERVES 644 MLN DLRS IN TWO WEEKS TO FEB 25, FED SAYS
</text>
</document>
<document id="96" name="Reuters-21578-96" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.acq</category>
<title>
INVESTMENT FIRMS CUT CYCLOPS &lt;CYL> STAKE
</title>
<text>
A group of affiliated New York
investment firms said they lowered their stake in Cyclops Corp
to 260,500 shares, or 6.4 pct of the total outstanding common
stock, from 370,500 shares, or 9.2 pct.
    In a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission,
the group, led by Mutual Shares Corp, said it sold 110,000
Cyclops common shares on Feb 17 and 19 for 10.0 mln dlrs.
</text>
</document>
<document id="97" name="Reuters-21578-97" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.oilseed</category>
<category>topics.soybean</category>
<category>topics.sorghum</category>
<category>topics.rye</category>
<category>topics.oat</category>
<category>topics.corn</category>
<category>topics.wheat</category>
<category>topics.grain</category>
<title>
ASCS TERMINAL MARKET VALUES FOR PIK GRAIN
</title>
<text>
The Agricultural Stabilization and
Conservation Service (ASCS) has established these unit values
for commodities offered from government stocks through
redemption of Commodity Credit Corporation commodity
certificates, effective through the next business day.
    Price per bushel is in U.S. dollars. Sorghum is priced per
CWT, corn yellow grade only.
     WHEAT     HRW   HRS    SRW   SWW   DURUM
 Chicago       --    3.04   2.98  --    --
 Ill. Track    --    --     3.16  --    --
 Toledo        --    3.04   2.98  2.90  --
 Memphis       --    --     3.05  --    --
 Peoria        --    --     3.11  --    --
 Denver        2.62  2.63  --    --    --
 Evansville    --    --    2.99  --    --
 Cincinnati    --    --    2.96  --    --
 Minneapolis   2.65  2.71  --    --    3.70
 Baltimore/
 Norf./Phil.   --    --    3.06  2.98  --
 Kansas City   2.87  --    3.17  --    --
 St. Louis     3.03  --    3.03  --    --
 Amarillo/
 Lubbock       2.64  --    --    --    --
               HRW   HRS   SRW   SWW   DURUM
 Lou. Gulf     --    --    3.16  --    --
 Portland/
 Seattle       3.07  3.08  --    3.10  3.70
 Stockton      2.78  --    --    --    --
 L.A.          3.23  --    --    --    4.05
 Duluth        2.65  2.71  --    --    3.70
 Tex. Gulf     3.10  --    3.16  --    --
             CORN  BRLY  OATS  RYE   SOYB  SORG
 Chicago     1.47  --    --    --    4.81  2.49
 Ill. Track  1.49  2.04  --    --    4.85  2.52
 Toledo      1.41  2.04  1.50  --    4.78  2.39
 Memphis     1.59  1.95  1.71  --    4.90  2.86
 Peoria      1.51  ---   --    --    4.80  2.60
 Denver      1.56  1.56  --    --    --    2.54
 Evnsvlle    1.54  2.04  1.50  2.17  4.90  2.61
 Cinci       1.52  2.04  1.50  2.17  4.85  2.58
 Mpls        1.34  1.75  1.50  1.85  4.68  --
 Balt/Nor/
 Phil        1.70  1.80  --    --    4.98  3.12
 KC          1.49  1.56  1.64  --    4.76  2.58
 St Lo       1.54  --    1.66  --    4.90  2.91
 Amarlo/
 Lubbck      1.84  1.40  --    --    4.75  2.92
 Lou Gulf    1.73  --    --    --    5.05  3.12
 Port/
 Seattle     1.87  2.10  1.68  --    --    --
 Stockton    2.18  2.23  2.10  --    --    4.00
 LA          2.54  2.50  --    --    --    4.38
 Duluth      1.34  1.75  1.50  1.85  4.68  --
 Tex Gulf    1.73  1.48  1.73  --    5.05  3.12
</text>
</document>
<document id="98" name="Reuters-21578-98" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.earn</category>
<title>
CORADIAN CORP &lt;CDIN> 4TH QTR NET
</title>
<text>
Shr profit three cts vs loss three cts
    Net profit 363,000 vs loss 197,000
    Revs 3,761,000 vs 2,666,000
    Year
    Shr profit one cent vs loss 37 cts
    Net profit 129,000 vs loss 1,715,000
    Revs 11.4 mln vs 10.9 mln
    Avg shrs 10,694,081 vs 4,673,253
</text>
</document>
<document id="99" name="Reuters-21578-99" dataset="ModApte-train">
<category>topics.money-supply</category>
<title>
26-FEB-1987
</title>
<text>
26-FEB-1987
</text>
</document>
</dataset>
